<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology on SCosme Blog</title><link>/categories/technology/</link><description>Recent content in Technology on SCosme Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WiFi</title><link>/post/wifi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/wifi/</guid><description>&lt;p>WiFi stands for Wireless Fidelity. This term was created by a branding company, and it only became popular in its abbreviated form. Describes a technology for creating wireless local area networks of devices based on the IEEE 802.11 standards, which are maintained by the LAN / MAN Standards Committee of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) LAN / MAN Standards Committee, (IEEE 802).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Robomart</title><link>/post/robotfood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/robotfood/</guid><description>&lt;p>BToday we know about a new system that allows the store to bring consumers&amp;rsquo; homes closer to making purchases, it is the Robomart mobile robotic food store, a vehicle developed by the Robomart company that is presented as the most accessible grocery store of the world and that stands out for availability, ease of use, speed and, of course, comfort.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hydraloop</title><link>/post/hydraloop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/hydraloop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Concerns about water scarcity are on the rise, companies are looking for more and more sophisticated ways to reduce water consumption. For the founder and CEO of Hydraloop, Arthur Valkieser, the answer was clear: to design a device to purify and reuse household water.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solar Pannels</title><link>/post/solar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/solar/</guid><description>&lt;p>Solar panels are a promising source of energy, solar panels crown the roofs of our homes, solar panels illuminate traffic signs, they even help to maintain power for spacecraft. But how do solar panels work?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Smart Assistants</title><link>/post/boot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/boot/</guid><description>&lt;p>Technologychatbots are virtual users that simulate a conversation with a human. Virtual Personal Assistants (VPAs) are born as a new standalone mobile app and are hosted on smart devices already known as Home Speakers or Home Devices, such as Google Home, Amazon Echo or Apple’s Home Pod. Chabot’s or conversational assistants are developed on websites, messaging apps, social networks or applications, and their main mode of interaction is through messages, whether voice or text.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mercedes-Benz</title><link>/post/mercedezbenz/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/mercedezbenz/</guid><description>&lt;p>When Mercedes Benz shows at the CES 2020 their “Vision AVTR” concept inspired by the movie ‘Avatar’. People did not expect much more from it. This is what the concepts are, just a project about: what could be done in the future thanks to the expression of ideas. They were wrong, the manufacturer has made this vehicle a reality and show what it is like to drive it on the street with its hypnotic design and those practically surreal wheels.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Holy Roller</title><link>/post/holy-roller/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/holy-roller/</guid><description>&lt;p>Is a Canadian Army Sherman Tank of the which fought across northwest Europe until the end of World War II, one of two Canadian tanks that fought in the second world war. This beautiful tank arrival to London in 1956.Today is located in the Victoria Park, London, Ontario.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>VR In Military Training</title><link>/post/vrmilitary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/vrmilitary/</guid><description>&lt;p>Awesome progressions continuously go hand in hand with the military world. When one nation invents a modern sort of weaponry, all the others are trying not to get as well distant behind. As the virtual reality industry was climbing up another summit, the military kept coming up with better approaches of implementing VR advances in military training. The five examples underneath are just a little obvious portion over the sea of openings that virtual reality can bring to the military segment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Amazon New Delivery Method</title><link>/post/amazon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/amazon/</guid><description>&lt;p>The e-commerce multinational Amazon received permission from the US government to start delivering packages using drones or unmanned aircraft, a fundamental step for the company&amp;rsquo;s future plans.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GPS (GLOBAL POSITIONING SYSTEM)</title><link>/post/gps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/gps/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Global Positioning System (GPS) is a satellite navigation system made up of a network of 24 satellites placed in orbit by the United States Department of Defense. GPS was originally intended for military applications, but in the 1980s, the government made the system available for civilian use. GPS works in any weather condition, anywhere in the world, 24 hours a day. There are no subscription fees or setup charges to use GPS.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Nanotechnology</title><link>/post/nano/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/nano/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nanotechnology is a type of technology with applications in various fields and that focuses on nano-scale materials and their properties. Nanotechnology, therefore, works with the nanometer (nm) as the unit of measurement (corresponding to one billionth of a meter).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality</title><link>/post/areality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/areality/</guid><description>&lt;p>Augmented Reality (AR) assigns the interaction between virtual environments and the physical world, making it possible for the two to intermingle through a technological device such as webcams, mobile phones (IOS or Android), tablets, among others.
In other words, AR inserts virtual objects into the physical context and displays them to the user using the interface of the real environment with the support of technology. This resource has been revolutionizing the way we deal with our tasks (and even those we assign to machines).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Technology in Soccer</title><link>/post/var/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/var/</guid><description>&lt;p>The VAR is the technology that is being used in soccer as an aid tool for referees in soccer matches.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How an electric car works?</title><link>/post/electric/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/electric/</guid><description>&lt;p>This sustainable mobility alternative gets its energy from rechargeable batteries. These are not only used to power vehicles, but are also used for the operation of windshield wipers and lights.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>