<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on SCosme Blog</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on SCosme Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robomart</title><link>/post/robotfood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/robotfood/</guid><description>&lt;p>BToday we know about a new system that allows the store to bring consumers&amp;rsquo; homes closer to making purchases, it is the Robomart mobile robotic food store, a vehicle developed by the Robomart company that is presented as the most accessible grocery store of the world and that stands out for availability, ease of use, speed and, of course, comfort.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hydraloop</title><link>/post/hydraloop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/hydraloop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Concerns about water scarcity are on the rise, companies are looking for more and more sophisticated ways to reduce water consumption. For the founder and CEO of Hydraloop, Arthur Valkieser, the answer was clear: to design a device to purify and reuse household water.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Budweiser Gardens</title><link>/post/london/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/london/</guid><description>&lt;p>Budweiser Gardens is a sports-entertainment centre, in London, Ontario, Canada – the largest such centre in southwestern Ontario. Until 2012, it was known as the John Labatt Centre.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Basic HTML Elements</title><link>/post/basic-elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/basic-elements/</guid><description>&lt;p>The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>